Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Classics, Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Classics, honors theses
1990-2007
SC4-3742
Stanford University. Department of Classics.
0.5 Linear feet (9 volumes in 1 box)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Department of Classics.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Information about Access
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Department of Classics.
Access Terms
Civilization, Classical; Student papers.
Collection Contents
- Theses, Acession ARCH-2011-152
  - Considine, Hollis, Principes quidem dei: how cult legitimates power through status., 2003 (Box 1)
  - Soldo, Matthew A., The remodeling of the new Bouleuterion at Athens., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Feldman, Todd Jonathan, Lapsus linguae: an automated Latin translator., 1990 (Box 1)
  - Iyer, Aditi, The petition of Petiese: studies in ancient Egyptian law., 2007 (Box 1)
  - Shearin, Wilson Henry, Signs of tradition: grappling with the legacy of ancient philosophy in Enneads IV.8., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Jost, Daniel Martin, The fragments of church unity: indications of ecclesiastical hierarchy in the Greek Christian inscriptions of late antique Athens and Crete., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Stocking, Charles, Language about Achilles: linguistic frame theory and the formula in Homeric poetics., 2002 (Box 1)
  - Stalla, Heidi Therese, An examination of the Poggio Civitate Banquet frieze plaque, and its relationship to the function of the monumental building., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Phillips, Darryl, The lex valeria cornelia and the election plan of Augustus., 1989 (Box 1)